<?xml version="1.0"?>
<articles xmlns="http://rerun.com" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://rerun.com schema/articles.xsd">
  <article id="1">
    <author id="1"/>
    <title>The Loneliest Human in the Universe</title>
    <preview>Al Worden on flying to the Moon and coming back to Earth.</preview>
    <content>My grandfather was probably as big an influence on me as anyone. He was a farmer in the upper part of the state of Michigan. He actually homesteaded the land. My granddad had a team of horses and everything was done with them. Back then it was one guy against the dirt on his farm and against Mother Nature trying to make a living out of owning a farm. I used to go up there and spend the summers with him on the farm and what I got from him was a sense of responsibility and a sense of perseverance and dedication to the job at hand.</content>
    <category>Exploring Space</category>
    <publishedDate>2014-05-24T16:41:25Z</publishedDate>
    <visibility>public</visibility>
  </article>
  <article id="2">
    <author id="2"/>
    <title>The Rise of the Snapchat Celebrity</title>
    <preview>Social Media platforms go through the phase of massive growth.</preview>
    <content>Snapchat is big, we&apos;re talking $4 billion big. This follows a trend of recent years with Social Media exploding that has seen successful IPOs from Facebook and Twitter, a buyout of Tumblr and even Google getting involved with Youtube and Google+. It&apos;s fairly safe to say that in the developed world everyone uses social media, it&apos;s where news breaks first, it&apos;s where people communicate and how things go viral. (It&apos;s probably equally safe to say we&apos;re witnessing the beginning of a massive tech bubble, but that&apos;s a topic for a different day).</content>
    <category>Tech Talk</category>
    <publishedDate>2014-05-24T16:45:25Z</publishedDate>
    <visibility>public</visibility>
  </article>
  <article id="3">
    <author id="3"/>
    <title>Apple&apos;s Beats Acquisition</title>
    <preview>How Apple is using cash to pay off risk.</preview>
    <content>There&apos;s been a lot of buzz recently about Apple&apos;s Beats Acquisition at $3.2 billion, it trumps all of Apple&apos;s acquisition purchases in 2013 combined by a good $2.7 billion. This is such a huge sum of money and so uncharacteristic that I was pretty shocked. My tweet at the time was: &quot;Don&apos;t do it this is as overpriced of a deal as the headphones themselves.&quot; My opinion hasn&apos;t really changed about the deal as a whole. I think it is grossly overpriced but Apple knows exactly what it doing. As a company that has $100 billion laying around, cash honestly doesn&apos;t mean much to them: the Beats acquisition is a risk mitigation strategy for entering the music streaming industry and if they can pay to reduce risk at the tune of $3.2 billion, they&apos;ll most definitely do it.</content>
    <category>Tech Talk</category>
    <publishedDate>2014-05-24T16:47:25Z</publishedDate>
    <visibility>public</visibility>
  </article>
  <article id="4">
    <author id="4"/>
    <title>Minqi&apos;s Article</title>
    <preview>Preview</preview>
    <content>Content</content>
    <category>Minqi</category>
    <publishedDate>2014-05-28T02:38:23Z</publishedDate>
    <visibility>authors</visibility>
  </article>
</articles>